luke1428.com 2019-07-17

# Disclosure/Privacy Policy

### **General Privacy Statement**

This blog is a personal blog written and edited by [me](https://luke1428.com/start-here/ "Welcome").

At Luke1428.com we do not collect personal information on those who browse this site unless the user provides it, such as in our comments section. We ask for personal information in this area of the site so that we can respond to comments or questions you post. Information is also collected at the Subscribe box so users can receive updated content via the email address they provide.

As per many websites, other types of information are collected from users when they interact here. _(i.e Google Adsense Policy – see below)._ We do this to analyze page views, referring sites (such as Facebook or Twitter), search engine terms used or the duration of ones visit. This information is non-personal in nature and is used by the owner to enhance the user experience at Luke1428.

We do not share personal information with third-parties, put your name on a spam list, nor sell your contact information to other companies.

### **Google Adsense Privacy Policy**

Google Adsense requires each blog showing ads from the Adsense program to display a “Privacy Policy.”

At www.luke1428.com, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by www.luke1428.com and how it is used.

**Log Files**

Like many other Web sites, www.luke1428.com makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

**Cookies and Web Beacons**

www.luke1428.com does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific iDnformation on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

**DoubleClick DART Cookie**

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on www.luke1428.com.

Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to www.luke1428.com and other sites on the Internet.

Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL – http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include …

Google Adsense

Amazon

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on www.luke1428.com send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

www.luke1428.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. www.luke1428.com’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.

### **Financial Arrangements Disclosure**

This blog accepts forms of cash advertising, sponsorship, paid insertions or other forms of compensation.

The compensation received will never influence the content, topics or posts made in this blog.

All advertising is in the form of advertisements generated by a third party ad network. Those advertisements will be identified as paid advertisements.

The owner(s) of this blog may be compensated to provide opinion on products, services, websites and various other topics. Even though the owner(s) of this blog receives compensation for our posts or advertisements, we always give our honest opinions, findings, beliefs, or experiences on those topics or products. The views and opinions expressed on this blog are purely the bloggers’ own. Any product claim, statistic, quote or other representation about a product or service should be verified with the manufacturer, provider or party in question.

This blog does not contain any content which might present a conflict of interest.

_The disclosure generated at http://www.disclosurepolicy.org._

#### Questions?

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to email me using the [Contact Form.](https://luke1428.com/about-me/contact/ "Contact")

_Last updated: Jan. 9 ,2014_
